The Streets Run Red is a horror film directed by Paul McAroni.
An aging detective and his hotheaded partner tirelessly pursue a serial killer who is right under their
nose in this gruesome, deplorable, disgusting new feature film from Ungovernable Films!
Ungovernable Films has set out this time to raise the bar on gore, obscenity, offensiveness, and
nauseating FX in this feature film about a serial killer pursued by two dedicated cops.
When the killer falls right into their laps without them realizing it, fact and fiction begin
to blur for the three men whose senses of identity seem less and less certain.
Football Announcer (voice), played by Lloyd Kaufman.
Alex, played by Dimas Bardales.
Detective Kemper, played by James Baglini.
Lt. Gumb, played by Ray DiNitto.
Forensics Officer, played by Arthur Williams III.
Django, played by Mike McCarthy.
The Wolf of Wall Street is a 2013 American epic biographical dark comedy crime film co-produced and directed
by Martin Scorsese, written by Terence Winter, and based on Jordan Belfort's 2007 memoir.
It loosely recounts Belfort's career as a stockbroker in New York City and how his firm, Stratton
Oakmont, engaged in rampant corruption and fraud on Wall Street, leading to his downfall.
The film stars Leonardo DiCaprio as Belfort; Jonah Hill as his business partner and friend Donnie Azoff; Margot Robbie as his second wife, Naomi Lapaglia;
Matthew McConaughey as his mentor and former boss Mark Hanna; and Kyle Chandler as FBI special agent Patrick Denham portraying Gregory Coleman.
It is DiCaprio's fifth collaboration with Scorsese.
DiCaprio and Warner Bros.
acquired the rights to Belfort's memoir in 2007, but
production was halted due to content restrictions.
It was later produced by the independent Red Granite Pictures.
The film was shot in New York in late 2012, using mostly 35mm film stock.
The film premiered in New York City on December 17, 2013, and was released
in the United States on December 25, by Paramount Pictures.
It was the first major American film to be released
exclusively through digital distribution.
It was a major commercial success, grossing $407 million worldwide during its
theatrical run, becoming Scorsese's highest-grossing film.
However, the film initially received considerable controversy for its moral ambiguity and lack of sympathy for victims, as well as its explicit, graphic sexual
content, extreme profanity (with at least 500 uses of the expletive "fuck"), depiction of hard drug use, and use of animals during production.
The film was initially rated NC-17 by the Motion Picture Association of America, but it was
shortly appealed for an R rating after Scorsese made slight changes to the film.
It set a Guinness World Record for the most instances of profanity in a film.
The film's financing became implicated in the 1Malaysia
Development Berhad corruption scandal; the U.S.
Department of Justice and the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission investigated
Red Granite Pictures, and producer Riza Aziz was arrested in 2019.
He was discharged in May 2020 on a 1,000,000
Malaysian ringgit (US$240,000) bail.
The film received positive reviews from critics and
appeared on several "best of the year" lists.
It was nominated for several awards, including five at the 86th Academy Awards ceremony: Best Picture, Best
Director, Best Adapted Screenplay, Best Actor (for DiCaprio) and Best Supporting Actor (for Hill).
DiCaprio won Best Actor – Musical or Comedy at the 71st Golden Globe Awards, where
the film was also nominated for Best Picture – Musical or Comedy.
The tone is dark.